14 days of using the viral skin TI are
their products worth it let's see this
brand is known to solve your skin
problem at an affordable price and most
of their products are suitable for all
skin types I take six products hoping
you can minimize my pores save my the
eye circles Brien my complexion and also
hydrate my skin tested Improvement for 2
weeks by me again let's start with this
barrier Essence toner although this is
an affordable toner but it feels
expensive the key ingredient is honic
acid which I love in a skincare product
because it gives intensive hydration to
the skin to brighten my complexion I
used thei brightening serum and moisture
J the oppty in the serum is a skin
brightening ingredient that specifically
targets hyperpigmentation and scars and
the ms9 cite in the moisture gel is
clinically proven to be 10 times more
effective than the ordinary one so here
is a picture comparison I wouldn't say
they are crazy result but it does it
drob slow and effectively for the Alaska
volcano PA clay stick mask the packaging
is literally a lazy girls dream because
it's so easy to apply all over the skin
without getting your hands dirir I
wonder who's the Lazy Girl definitely
not me anyways they have two colors
green and black and black color one is
meant to clear black hits plus
minimizing your pores I can feel my skin
has gotten smoother silkier every time I
use it and it doesn't feel drying at all
after leaving them on your skin next the
special thing about their eye cream is
that it has an automated Crystal
massager that you can massage around
your under eyes area and lastly the
seran sunscreen contains spf50 and it is
easy to carry everywhere that's it I
still think the products are overall
amazing considering the price I would
100% recommend adona ni cite serum and
moisture gel and also the volcanic po
stickk you know is more worth it if you
are buying and Watson sell because you
can get 60% discount on the second item
and a 13 R instant reate if you are a
Watson Club member so if you're a
student who's on a budget but you also
want good skare I strongly believe you
know where to go